https://www.entltd.com/privacy-policy/

Close
Ear, Nose and Throat, Ltd, is staying up-to-date on the latest information. We continue to monitor Governor Northam's directions as well as the CDC and WHO, please remember, despite all the precautions and cleaning, an office cannot reduce the risk to zero; it is the patient's final decision to come in for an appointment. Please note: ONLY THE PATIENT IS ALLOWED INTO THE OFFICE, MINORS WITH ONE PARENT.Learn More
Request Appointment
Patient Portal
Home
About Us
About Us
Our Staff
Our Locations
Ear & Hearing
Hearing Aid Styles
Hearing Aid Pricing (with financing options)
Hearing Aid Fitting & Counseling
Hearing Aid Service & Repairs
Hearing Aid Accessories
Pediatric Hearing Aids
Bone Anchored Hearing Devices
Balance & Tinnitus
Tinnitus
Tinnitus Treatments
Skull Base Tumors
Transnasal Esophagoscopy (TNE)
Tumors
Resources
Patient Forms
Insurance
Financing
HIPAA Statement
Contact
Search
Search for:
This
privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with
how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online.
PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information
that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact or
locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read
our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect,
use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in
accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When
ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter
your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to
help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We
collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a
newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We
may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase,
sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication,
surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To send
periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.To
follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
How do we protect your information?
Our
website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known
vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We
use regular Malware Scanning.
Your
personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only
accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to
such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In
addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure
Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We
implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits or
accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All
transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or
processed on our servers.
Do we use ‘cookies’?
We
do not use cookies for tracking purposes.
You
can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you
can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings.
Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to
learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If
you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more
efficient may not function properly.
Third-party disclosure
We
do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally
Identifiable Information.
Third-party links
Occasionally,
at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on
our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy
policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and
activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity
of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google’s
advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles.
They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google,
as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of
the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits
to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of
the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
Demographics and Interests Reporting:
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act:
CalOPPA
is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online
services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond
California to require any person or company in the United States (and
conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally
Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous
privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected
and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more
at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users
can visit our site anonymously.
Once
this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as
a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our
Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the
page specified above.
You
will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
On our
Privacy Policy Page
Can
change your personal information:
By
calling us
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We
honor Do Not Track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising
when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It’s
also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When
it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age
of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents
in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection
agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites
and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.
We
do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
The
Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the
United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in
the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the
Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is
critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal
information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals
have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and
processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that
individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that
individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate
and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The
CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes
requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails
stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
Send
information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
Not use
false or misleading subjects or email addresses.Identify
the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.Include
the physical address of our business or site headquarters.Monitor
third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.Honor
opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.Allow
users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us.
Follow the instructions at the bottom of each
email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If
there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using
the information below.
Ear, Nose and Throat LTD | 885 Kempsville Rd. Suite 304 Norfolk, VA 23502 |
Office:(757) 623-0526
